JONGSUN PARK

Junior Web Developer & UI/UX Designer

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a highly self-motivated and self-taught developer and designer. My first experience in the digital industry is building websites by CMS (WordPress). I used my spare time to learn new skills and trends. It boosts my working speed and results.

I'd like to learn the core of programming and design to achieve efficiency for both client and user. and keep eyes on trends with new tech to not be outdated.

EXPERIENCE

FAT FISH MARKETING, IRE — JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

DEC 2018 - APR 2020

Creating WordPress, Shopify website for simple website.

Using InVision / Adobe XD to design an application prototype and build the application view side with React Framework

HANSSEM, KO — INTERIER COORDINATOR

JAN 2015 - SEP 2017

Sale to retail customers and meeting with HQ coworkers as store manager. also manage private marketing and have responsibility for entire sales in the shop.

EDUCATION

DKIT, IRE — Certificate in User Experience Design (LV 7)

FEB 2021 - NOW

This course contains web development using bootstrap, ux concepts and visual communication. It uses adobeXD and photoshop for implementation.

DKIT, IRE—Certificate in Programming (LV 6)

SEP 2018 - SEP 2019

Covered initial program theory and languages. It's covered HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, PHP etc.

Yeungnam University, KO— Business Administration and Chinese Literature (B.A)

MAR 2008 - MAR 2015

Double major in Business Administration and linguistics in Chinese with 1 year on exchange in Wuhan, China.

1 Barrack Street
Dundalk, A91 V1K7
(+353) 87 388 3948
jongsun250@gmail.com
linkedin/in/jongsun-park

SKILLS

HTML + CSS + JavaScript

Node.js + Express

React.js (2 yr)

AdobeXD + Invision

Photoshop + Illustrator + InDesign

CMS (WordPress / Shopify) (2 yr)

CERTIFICATES (UDEMY)

The Advanced Web Developer Bootcamp by Colt Steele

React - The Compele Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Reduct) by Maximillian

NodeJS- The Complete Guide (MVC, REST APIs, GraphQL, Deno) by Maximillian

Graphic Design Materclass by Lyndsay

Master Web Design in Photoshop by Chrstian Doru Barin.

LANGUAGES

Korean - Native English - Intermediate Chinese - Intermediate